BAKARE, ASHIAT ABIDEMI

Ashiatbakare98@gmail.com

+234-703-434-5448

10, Nnokam street, UST, Port-Harcourt

CAREER OBJECTIVE

An enthusiastic and versatile graduate with keen interest in becoming part of a viable organization that facilitates personal development and career advancement. I aim to contribute to the achievement of organization's objectives and goals by combining my personal skills, academic achievements and work experience in any given role.

SKILLS AND PERSONAL TRAITS

- Effective communication skills
 - Team work and highly dedicated
- Time Management skill
- Analytical skill
- Problem solving skill
- Self-motivated
- Leadership skill
 - Result oriented

COMPUTER SKILLS

Proficient in the use of MS office tools such as MS-Word, MS-Excel and MS-PowerPoint

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

University of Lagos

July 2014 - November 2019

B.Sc. Petroleum and Gas engineering (First Class)

Relevant Courses: Reservoir, Drilling and Production Engineering, Petroleum economics, Process dynamics and control

Research Project: Gas well production optimization using dynamic nodal analysis, response surface modelling and firefly algorithm

Stars Comprehensive College

August 2008 - July 2014

West African Examination Council and National Examination Council Certificates

ACHIEVEMENTS

Diploma in Environmental and Petroleum Technology Management August 2017

Joint professional and Training Support International

Attended Health, Safety and Environment (HSE) level 1 and 2 training July 2017

Affiliate member of Offshore, Onshore, Oil and Gas Professionals (O3GP) August 2017

EXPERIENCE

Monitoring and Evaluation (M & E) officer (NYSC)

March 2020 - March 2021

Solina Centre for International Development and Research (SCIDaR)

- Data collection, gathering and analysis to make informed programmatic decisions
- Data monitoring and evaluation to identify and correct discrepancies and report preparation from evaluated data
- Participating in problem solving sessions to tackle specific program issues and implementing immediate next steps
- Coordinating activities of reporting staffs and ensuring availability of all data collection tools

Intern Operator

July 2018 - December 2018

Nigerian Pipelines and Storage Company, Ibadan Depot, Apata

- Daily monitoring and management of the depot products in storage and those up for sales
- Monitoring Product reception into the depot and product pumping out of the depot
- Managing depot's waste water for product recovery and safe disposal
- Communication of the Depot's operations with the Area office
- Ensuring Safe practices in the depot and in general equipment handling
- Daily product testing and Standardization in the depot

VOLUNTEER WORK

- Head of Society of Petroleum Engineers (SPE) university of Lagos Chapter Volunteers
- Volunteer Logistics Committee for Professor Ayodele Awojobi Design Competition (PAADC)
- Head of Logistics Committee for Society of Petroleum Engineers (SPE) university of Lagos Chapter event, The Industry Discourse (TID)

REFEREE

Available on request